放松
对不起我迟到了 甜瓜小姐
I'm sorry I was late, Miss Melons.
我保证这种事不会再发生了
I promise it'll never happen again.
坏女孩高中
抱歉 我们能休息一会儿吗
I'm sorry, can we take a short break?
我有个小问题
I just have a tiny question.
好吧 快点 斑比
Okay. Make it quick, Bambi.
-黑板可是租来的  -好
- Blackboard's a rental. - Right.
我只是在想 我真的应该惩罚她吗
Just wondering, should I really be punishing her?
当然 这是杂志存在的前提
Uh, yeah. That's kind of the premise of the magazine.
不 我明白
No, I get that.
也许她迟到是有原因的
It's just that maybe she was tardy for a reason.
有人问过她吗 也许家里出了事情
Did anyone ask her? Maybe there's trouble at home.
性感问题
Sexy trouble.
这些是坏女孩高中的淘气女生
These are the naughty schoolgirls of Bad Girl High.
她们做了坏事
They do bad stuff. - Mm-hmm.
你打她们的屁股 这就样
You spank their bottoms. That's the whole story.
一般来说 是这样
Typically, yes.
但这次可能不是
Uh, but maybe not in this instance.
好吗 斯塔西 你起来
Okay? Staci, please rise.
嘿 告诉我
Hey, you can tell me.
你今天早上迟到有什么原因吗
Was there a reason that you were late this morning?
我爸爸工作到很晚
my dad was working late.
对 因为他是个警察
Right. 'Cause he's a cop
他和他的搭档里克上夜班
and he works the graveyard shift with his partner, Rico.
是的 是的 还发生了枪战
Yeah. Yeah, and there was a shootout.
里克没能挺过来
And Rico didn't make it,
所以你在安慰你爸爸
so you were comforting your dad.
自从妈妈去世后 他就只有我了
Well, since Mom died, I'm all he's got.
就因为这个她要被打屁股吗
And for this she is getting spanked?
我们应该支持她
We should be supporting her,
而不是因为她的善良而惩罚她
not punishing her for her kindness.
时代在改变 菲尔
Times they are a-changing, Phil.
斯塔西需要拿到她的学位
Staci needs to be getting her degree
这样她才能把这种同情心带到工作中
so she can bring this compassion to the workforce.
我不知道你他妈在讲什么
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about,
但这个热情是我们需要的
but this is the energy we need.
菲尔 我提出了一个很重要的论点
I'm trying to make an important point here, Phil.
这不是《风骚女子》 我们不是开辩论的
This isn't "Minx." We don't do points.
斯塔西 趴下
Stacy, bend over.
舔苹果
And, uh, lick the apple.
给我 给我美好的爱情
♪ Gimme, gimme good lovin' ♪
每晚
♪ Every night ♪
再见了 双头屌
现在已经没事了 孩子
♪ You know it's all right now. child. ♪
-嘿 特莉  -嗨
- Hey, Terri. - Hi.
-看起来不错啊 乔尔  -谢了 乔伊斯
- Ooh, lookin'good, Joel. - Ah, thanks, Joyce.
真好
Great.
阿丽斯代尔 他的皮毛焕然一新了啊
Oh, Alisdair. He got his fur washed.
嘿 淫荡女学生又开始上课了
Hey. Carnal Coeds back in session,
-是吗  -希望是
- are they? - I wish.
不知怎么的 我要在坏女孩高中获得终身教职了
I'm somehow on the tenure track at Bad Girl High.
说到这个 如果有什么办法
Speaking of, if there's any way
能让我多参与到风骚女子中
I can be more involved at "Minx"...
中间插页照片拍的怎么样了
What happened to centerfold coordination?
这是一个月仅需要两天就能完成的工作
Well, turns out that's a two-day-a-month job,
但我整个月都有新灵感
but I have 30 days of inspiration.
是的 当然 那你有什么想法
Well yeah, sure. What do you have in mind?
我可以做
Um, I could always do the, um...
或者你知道的
Or, um, you know the, uh...
你知道吗 你有想法了
You know what? You just have a think
-就告诉我  -好的
and you let me know. - Okay.
-好吗  -早上好啊 亲爱的
- Okay? - Bonjour, ma belle.
早上好
Bonjour.
猜猜看哪个被选用了
Guess what you get to approve?
天呐 真的吗 已经好了吗
Oh, my God, really? Already?
-他们看起来怎么样  -很不错
- How do they look? - Oh, decent.
我觉得下次我应该再黑两度
I think maybe next time I'd go two stops darker.
你说吧
But, uh, you tell me.
比我想象的还要好
Oh, they're even better than I imagined.
谢天谢地你也这么想
Oh, thank God you think so too!
我很喜欢我们在诉说什么的感觉
I love that we're saying something, you know?
你看到他眼中的痛苦了吗
You see the pain in his eyes?
就好像他把几代女性遭受的骚扰
It's like he's internalizing the harassment
都内化了
endured by generations of women.
就在那时
That's actually the moment
他知道了我们付他多少钱
he found out what we're paying him.
-好吧  -嘿 孩子
- Oh, well-- - Hey, kid.
-怎么了  -准备好了吗
- Yeah? - You ready to go?
当然 早就整装待发了
Yes. Been ready my whole life.
为杂志卖广告位
Just selling ad space for my magazine.
-他要带你一起去吗  -对
- He's taking you with him? - Yup.
童年梦想的巅峰了
Culmination of a childhood dream.
没什么大不了
No big deal.
这可是件大事
It is a big deal.
-有事随时联系我  -好
- I'm here if you need me. - Great.
好极了
Right on!
很多买家我都不认识
I'm not recognizing a lot of these buyers.
我提到的那些非营利组织任务为导向的公司
What happened to the mission-driven nonprofits
-怎么了  -我们需要能
- I mentioned? - Oh, we need companies
真正给我们钱的公司
who can actually give us money.
这就是我们的资金来源
That's kind of how we finance this operation
除非你想把《风骚女子》卖到49.99美元
unless you wanna sell "Minx" for 49.99.
-我会买的  -酷啊 有一个买家
- I would pay that. - Oh, cool. Well, that's one.
我们能把女权联邦信用社加上吗
Oh, can we add the Feminist Federal Credit Union?
乔伊斯 我的广告工作人员做了功课的
Joycie, my ad guys did their homework.
这些都是很有实力的公司
These are all huge gets.
如果这些人中有人想加入我们就很幸运了 好吧
We'll be lucky if any of these people want in, okay?
别紧张
Don't be nervous.
做个优雅的哈佛人就好了
Just be your classy Harvard self.
-瓦萨人  -随你怎么说
- Vassar. - Whatever.
女性解放 这是什么意思
Women's liberation. What does it mean?
我来告诉你这对我意味着什么
Well, I'll tell you what it means to me.
这意味着要把女性从每年4亿美元的
It means liberating women from the $400 million
可支配收入中解放出来
in disposable income they spend every year.
我们的版式将女性解放的戒律
Our format melds the precepts of female emancipation
与成熟但主题恰当的内容结合起来
with mature but thematically appropriate content.
我们认为我们创造了一种女性凝视
We think of ourselves as creating the female gaze.
女人是性感的 但这是从大脑开始的
Women are sexual, but it starts with the brain.
你们看 一期的《时尚》在一个月内
You see, one issue of "Cosmo" sold over 3 million copies
卖出了300多万份
in one month.
为什么呢 因为老伯特·雷诺兹露出了
Why? Cause that good old Burt Reynolds
给喜欢硬的女人
他毛茸茸的大腿
showed his hairy thighs.
不合你的心意 也许也不合我的
Not your cup of tea, maybe not mine.
渴吗
我们有罐
但谁在乎呢
Who cares?
我们在说的是钱
'Cause we're talking
很多钱
about money--a lot of money.
小盒子里竟然承载了如此多的美味
我猜这就是
And I'm guessing that's what--
小盒子里竟然承载了如此多的美味
So much flavor in one little box.
沃尔夫哈根啤酒
三杯啤酒让我赞不绝口
沃尔夫哈根
Wolfhagen.
三杯啤洒让我赞不绝囗
Three beers takes me from bow to wow!
美味内裤
Yum-derwear.
多汁的中心的糖衣
A candy coating for that juicy center.
我告诉你 《风骚女子》会展示给他们看的
I'm telling you, Minx is gonna give it to'em
我们会做出好杂志给他们看的
and we're gonna give it to'em good.
也许两个 但快乐之园呢
Maybe two, but Pleasure Garden?
他们家大业大 但他们从来没有办法
I mean, they're huge and they never had a way
直接向女性营销 现在他们可以了
to market directly to women. Now they do.
所以有了10到15个广告 这就可以为我们的书买单了
So 10, 15 ads-- that alone pays for our book.
伙计 我们要让全美国的小妞
Kid, we're gonna wet the panties
都湿裤裆了
of every chick in America.
嘿 你要去哪 车在那边
Hey, where're you going? The car is that way.
怎么了 乔伊斯 事情进展很顺利
What's the problem, Joyce? That went great.
这些广告是对所有妇女的侮辱
The ads were an affront to all womenkind.
还有那些产品 堵嘴球和有着突起棱纹的避孕套
And those products-- ball gags and French ticklers?
怎么了 你讨厌做爱吗
What's the pr-- do you hate sex?
不 不 就是 不是
No. No! It's--no.
我 就是
I--it's just--it's--it's--
不 这本应该是私密的
No. It's supposed to be private is all.
只是像我这样的人 我们不会讨论
And it's just people like me, we don't discuss...
阴道润滑剂
vaginal lubricant.
别这么自命不凡
Don't be such a snob.
世界又不是在帕萨迪纳市开始和结束的
The world does not begin and end in Pasadena.
但我们的杂志可能会
Yeah. Our magazine might, though.
好吧
Okay.
如果你想要某种类型的读者
If want a certain kind of reader,
我们就得刊登同等次产品的广告
we have to advertise upscale products.
好吗 我们要用连裤袜和香水等
Okay? We gotta lure them in with pantyhose
这些让她们感觉安全的东西引诱她们
and perfume--things that make them feel safe.
你以为我从没想过要凯迪拉克和鱼子酱吗
You think I never tried to get Cadillacs and caviar?
有品位的公司从来不会把他们的广告
Classy companies have never put their ad
放在一对奶子上
across from a pair of titties.
他们也肯定不会靠近屌的
And they're certainly not going anywhere near a dong.
是不会 你这么说显然不会
Yeah, no. Obviously not when you talk about it like that.
也许我直接和高端买家谈
Maybe it's better if I just speak with
会更好
the high-end buyers directly.
怎么
What?
她觉得她能做什么
What does she think she's gonna do?
给洗发水公司打个电话吗
Just cold call a shampoo company?
-道格  -我带她来
- Doug. - I mean, I only
只是为了让那些人知道
brought her along so that these guys would know
我是认真的
that I was legit.
廷 她就
Tin, she's like the, um...
她就像引擎盖上的装饰品
she's like the hood ornament, right?
但我才是那辆车
But me, I'm the whole car.
-你说完了吗  -没有 永远说不完
- You done? - No, I'm never done.
你知道的 不过你说吧
You know that. But go ahead.
我很痛心地说
It pains me to say this,
但他们有点喜欢引擎盖上的装饰
but they kind of liked the hood ornament.
有个叫快乐之园的公司 他们想要加入
Pleasure Garden called. They want in.
-别开玩笑  -但他们的内部人员
- No kidding? - But their in-house guys
不知道如何为女士们做广告
don't know how to do an ad for ladies,
所以他们想让我们为他们设计
so they want us to spec it for them.
乔伊斯会喜欢这个的
Joyce is gonna love this.
你们这些傻瓜这次中大奖了
You jokers hit the jackpot on this one.
这个广告不言自明
This ad is gonna write itself.
向路西法之角致敬
All hail Lucifer's Horn.
这个两头是怎么回事
What's the deal with the double ends?
《风骚女子》的妞们是有两个洞还是怎么的
Those "Minx" chicks got two fox holes or something?
这是给女同性恋的 佩里
It's for lesbians, Perry.
唯一不会被你吸引的女人
You know, the only women not attracted to you.
让我和她们待五分钟
Give me five minutes with 'em.
五分钟正合适
Five minutes seems about right.
肯定还有比这更好的广告商
There have to be better advertisers than that.
你知道观众是哪些人群吗
Do you get who your audience is?
《风骚女子》是给那些性开放的女人看的
I mean, "Minx" is for sexually liberated chicks, okay?
是的 但我们的阴茎是为了政治目的 明白吗
Yes, but our penis is for political purposes, okay?
这是关于权力动态的转变
It's about shifting power dynamics
和性别补偿
and gender reparations.
孩子 我不想打断你
Kid, I hate to break it to you,
但你不能控制读者们
but you can't control what readers are gonna do
用那些消防员的小弟弟做什么
with that fireman's schlong.
有些人甚至会对着它打飞机
Some might even jerk off to it.
我不想帮他们这样做
I don't have to help them do that.
也没人要求你这么做
And no one's asking you to.
我让我最好的广告人去做了
I got my best ad guys on it.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我本可以做任何事的
I could have done anything with my life.
我的美国研究生入学考试考的很好
I did quite well on the GRE.
力量在你手中
天啊 和他的大腿一样大啊
Oh, my God. It's as big as his thigh!
佩德罗 请再加点茶
Oh, Pedro, more tea please.
谢谢你 这太酷了
Thank you so much. This is so cool.
我觉得自己像个特工
I feel like a secret agent.
是 这可能会永远是个秘密
Yeah, well, it might stay a secret forever.
我和你说 道格选的广告能在《风骚女子》上架前
Doug's ads, I'm telling you, they could kill "Minx"
就把它毁掉
before it even gets off the ground.
我觉得你反应过激了 谢谢
I think you're overreacting. Thank you.
是吗 真的吗 那你就舒服的做着指甲
－ Oh, really? You do? Okay, so would be comfortable
看着满页
getting your nails done, reading a magazine
-都是双头屌的杂志吧  -双头 双头
full of double dongs. - Double--doubles?
-你是说两个吗  -普里格两姐妹啊
Doubles, did you say? - The Prigger sisters.
-嗨 罗斯先生  -哈喽 罗斯先生
- Hi, Mr. Ross. - Hello, Mr. Ross.
培根
Oh, bacon.
你们这代的女性真是什么都吃
Your generation of ladies-- not afraid to eat.
食物确实能让人活下来
- Oh. - It does keep one alive.
我妻子 她每天早上都要吃半个葡萄柚
My wife, she swears by half a grapefruit each morning
然后周三 她会加些白软干酪
and then on Wednesday, she adds cottage cheese.
我在球场上见过贝西
Well, I've seen Bitsy on the courts,
她看起来非常苗条
and she's looking incredibly trim.
是的 要是她像乔伊斯那样是正手击球就好了
Yeah. If only she had Joyce's forehand.
哈哈 好吧 她用那讨厌的反手击球
Oh, ha ha, well, she more than makes up for it
弥补了这一切
with that nasty backhand of hers.
煎饼
Oh, pancakes.
我看到有人在款待自己啊
I see someone is treating themselves.
她们怎么敢
How dare they!
每到星期四 我都 允许贝西
"On Thursdays I permit Bitsy
把她的腰带松开一个扣
to loosen her girdle by one notch."
哦 她闻了闻两个蓝莓
Oh, she sniffs two blueberries
然后吞下一把右旋糖甙
and then downs a fistful of Dexedrine.
那老古董是怎么
How does that fossil
当了这么久的权的
stay in power?
罗斯先生在这里当了多久的总统
Mr. Ross has been president here for, what,
-30年吗  -是的
- like, 30 years? - Yeah.
他是最有钱的
He's the richest.
这些男人都喜欢拍马屁
And all these men love to suck up.
你知道这里不只有茶话会和网球 乔伊斯
You know it's not just tea parties and tennis here, Joyce.
这是做生意的地方
This is a place of business.
我打赌这里有人能教我
I bet there are people here who could teach me
一些广告方面的知识
a thing or two about advertising.
就像 给我我需要的工具
You know, like, give me the tools that I need
说服道格让我按自己的方式去做
to convince Doug to let me do it my way.
是啊 我是说 现在高尔夫球场上的CEO
Well, yeah, I mean, there's more CEOs on the golf course
比这个道格这辈子见过的还多
right now than this Doug fella has met in his entire life.
欧文 我听说了锦标赛的事
Mr. Irving. Oh, I was so sorry
我很遗憾
to hear about the tournament.
发生在你侄女身上的事 太滑稽了
What happened to your niece, it was a travesty.
她在球场上可比不上你
She doesn't hold a candle to you on the courts.
你就像一只瞪羚
You were like a gazelle.
你真好 当我有
That is very sweet. Um, while I have you--
我在一个新的领域里
I'm in a new entrepreneurial venture,
我想听听你的意见
and I'd love to pick your brain.
怎么进行广告购买
How do you make ad buys?
是基于代理还是企业对企业
Is that agency based or is that business to business?
我是来放松的 普里格小姐
I came here to relax, Miss Prigger,
不是来教育无礼的年轻女子
not educate impudent young ladies.
你对广告合作伙伴的要求是什么
What do you look for in advertising partners?
只要大致描述一下就够了
Just a vague description would suffice.
那是本有鸡巴的杂志
It's a magazine with a penis.
听起来很不错
That sounds very nice.
是的 谢谢 非常感谢
Yeah, thank you. Thank you so much.
-我喜欢看图片  -是吗
- I like looking at pictures. - Do you?
当他为国效力时
"While he's serving his country,
她在为自己服务
she's serving herself."
用越战啊 我不知道 兄弟们
Vietnam? I don't know, guys.
也许我们可以把政治排除在外
Maybe we leave politics out of it.
这把枪倒是很酷 是吧
Well, it's a cool gun though, isn't it?
是的 她也有自己的武器
Yeah. And she has a weapon of her own.
看到这对称性了吗
See the symmetry?
不 我明白了 接下来是什么 兄弟
No, I got it. What's next, guys?
没人会知道你肮脏的小秘密
"No one will know your dirty little secret."
有点侮辱人 对吧
Kinda shamey, right?
我们想让她们买
I mean, we want them to buy it.
-嗯嗯  -是的
- Yeah. Yeah. - Okay. Uh...
当你没有戒指的时候 这是另一个最好的选择
"When you don't have a ring, it's the next best thing"
好吧 你太刻薄了
Okay, that's just mean.
但这并不意味着不是真的
Doesn't make it not true, though.
兄弟们 我们不想霸凌这些女人
Guys, we don't wanna bully these women.
我们是想让她们爽一下
We wanna get them off.
好 我们确实有另一个
Okay. We did have this one other one.
这可能更接近你要找的
It might be a little closer to what you're looking for.
-看看  -我们在想
- Let's see it. - We were thinking
女人喜欢力量 对吧
women love strength, right? Mm?
相信机器
"Trust the machine."
好了 谢谢 兄弟们 太好了
All right. Thanks, guys. Great.
好吧 失败了
Well, that was a bust.
他们只愿意和我聊
All they're willing to talk to me about
我的身材和网球
is my figure and my tennis game.
你的正手球打得太棒了
Oh, your forehand was a marvel.
但我猜他们叫它男生俱乐部是有原因的
But I guess they call it a boys club for a reason.
天啊 又怎么了
Oh, my God. What now?
-呃 普里格小姐  -嗨
- Uh, Miss Prigger, um...- Yeah, hi.
小鸟告诉我你在俱乐部里
Little bird told me that you've been conducting business
做生意
on club grounds.
是啊 反正我也想
Yeah, I was trying to, anyway.
你们做起来感觉很简单
You boys make it look so easy.
然后我意识到你是在向年轻女性
Then I became aware that you are marketing explicit
推销露骨的可耻内容
and scandalous content to young women?
我可不会说妇女解放运动可耻
I wouldn't call women's liberation scandalous.
你一直都是俱乐部的
Well, you always were
激进煽动者 不是吗
the club rabble-rouser, weren't you?
我不想刻太毒舌 道格
I don't wanna be mean, Doug,
但这些广告让我恨我自己
but these make me hate myself,
但是我爱我自己耶
and I love myself.
这让我讨厌男人
These make me hate men.
让我有点恨你
And they kind of make me hate you.
-哦 是的 肯定  -请冷静一点
- Oh, yeah. For sure. - Please simmer down.
所以我才把你们叫来
That's why I brought you guys in here,
从女性的角度来看看 对吧
to get a female perspective, right?
我不知道 斑比
So I don't know. Bambi,
你为什么要买振动棒
what would make you buy a vibrator?
我不知道 我已经有满满一抽屉了
I don't know--I have a whole drawer full already.
但是 我不知道 也许我希望它能挠得
But, I don't know, maybe if it tickled a little deeper
更深一点或者 它能
or if it went, like, a--
就像有旋律
Like a syncopation thing.
或者可以播放音乐什么的
Or maybe if it played music.
哦 价格也很重要 我得精打细算
Oh, also price is important. I'm on a budget.
这些都很棒
These are all really great.
有什么想法能把这些想法做出来吗
Any ideas how to take that brainstorm and put it on paper?
没有
No.
我想我不能做杂志广告人了
I guess I can't be a magazine advertising person.
猜猜谁用鱼叉叉住了一头鲸鱼
Guess who harpooned a whale!
耶
Yeah!
然后他说 我个人觉得裸体很恶心
And then he said, "I personally find nudity
但我相信你冒的这个险会
to be distasteful, but I believe this venture of yours
受到现代女性的欢迎
will be popular with modern women."
我觉得他说“现代”是一种侮辱
And I think he meant "modern" like an insult,
但我能得到的我一定要
but I will take what I can get.
贝克利化妆品 我从来没听说过
Beckley Cosmetics? I never heard of them.
这只是罗斯先生众多资产中的一笔
It's just one of Mr. Ross' many holdings,
如果你研究过高端市场
a fact that you would know
你就会知道这个事实
if you had researched upscale markets.
贝克利市场是老年人的家
Beckley's market is the old folks' home.
-80岁以下的人都不穿  -他们在兔子身上做测试
No one under 80 wears it. - And they test on bunnies.
你能不能别再提兔子了
Oh, my God. Enough with the bunnies, okay?
-它们只会拉屎做爱  -我们也是啊
All they do is shit and fuck. - So do we.
这家伙买了多少广告
How many ads is this guy buying?
我们明天在俱乐部的演讲结束后就知道了
We will know after our pitch at the club tomorrow,
5点整的夏夜晚宴上
5:00 on the dot during the Summer Soiree.
太棒了 记得告诉我进展如何
Great. Well, let me know how it goes.
呃 其实
Uh, y--well, actually,
我建议罗斯先生
I--I suggested to Mr. Ross
也见见你
that he sit with you as well.
出于尊重 你懂的
Just out of respect, you know,
这样我们都有发言权
so that we both have a voice in the process.
他想见你的男性出版商
He wants to meet your male publisher.
好吧 在当权派中存在
－ All right, fine. There is a patriarchal mindset
一种父权制思维
amongst the establishment.
但这正是我们需要《风骚女子》的原因 好吗
But that is exactly why we need "Minx," okay?
是要废除这些压迫制度
It's to dismantle these systems of oppression.
一次一个口红广告
One lipstick ad at a time.
我想公开声明 这简直是胡扯
I wanna go on record and say that this is bullshit.
这个富家闺秀会
It's a rich-girl-favor meeting
我会去的 我会尽我所能
and I will come and I will give it my best,
但如果这行不通
but if this doesn't work,
你们都得同意快乐花园
you're all in on the Pleasure Garden.
你的怀疑是我的动力
Your skepticism is my fuel.
-哦 我们在发抖  -嗯
- Ooh, we're shaking. - Mm-hmm.
准备好 朋友们 我们要去“娘们儿”俱乐部了
Saddle up, partners, we're going to the "cunty" club.
如果你要拖我
- Um... - Well, if you're gonna
去什么无聊的派对
drag me to some lame party,
我要带能玩的人去
I'm bringing people who can hang.
他们在那里不会玩得很开心的
Well, it's just they won't have fun there.
俱乐部是一种传染性气体
-Clubs are a gas.
盖蒂和我曾经在梅德斯通的
JP Getty and I used to make love
高尔夫球场上做过爱
on the golf course at Maidstone.
我最喜欢和殖民者在一起玩耍了
Mm. And I love mingling with the colonizers.
廷 你很喜欢能量棒吧
Tins, you do love a raw bar.
我更喜欢免费酒吧
Not as much as I love an open bar.
哇
Oh. Wow.
人越多越开心嘛
The more the merrier, then.
看起来是引擎盖装饰在开车了
Looks like the hood ornament's driving the car now.
我已经计划了一整天
♪ I had whole day plannin' ♪
我来了
♪ All kind of I'm comin' ♪
我已经计划了一整天
♪ I had whole day plannin' ♪
我来了
♪ All kind of I'm comin' ♪
他们说会有人
♪ They said there will be people ♪
他们不在乎麻烦
♪ And they don't care 'bout trouble ♪
但告诉他们别为我担心
♪ But tell them don't worry with me ♪
是另一回事 1963
♪ Is a different thing, 1963 ♪
因为路上
♪ Because the road... ♪
乔伊斯
Joyce.
-你好 格伦  -我 呃
- Hello, Glenn. - I, uh--
我没想到你会来
I-I didn't think you'd be here.
我还是属于这里的 所以
Uh, well, I do still belong, so...
对
Right. Um...
格兰尼斯 你把我的围巾放哪了
Glenneth, where'd you put my wrap?
乔伊斯 这是我的朋友凯蒂
Joyce, this is-- this is my friend, Kitty.
凯蒂·劳森
－ Kitty Lawson.
天啊 当然 是 我曾经
Oh, my God, of course. Yeah. I used to--
我以前照顾过你
I used to babysit you.
我八岁的时候
When I was eight.
你用冰块和土豆给我扎了耳洞
You pierced my ears with an ice cube and a potato.
对 是这样
That's right. I did do that for you.
-洞变大了  -哦
- The holes stretched. - Oh.
我的耳垂太娇嫩了
My lobes are so delicate.
它们可能是用薄纱做的
They might as well be made of gossamer.
-艾玛  -你好吗
Emma! - How are you?
槌球派对上你怎么没来
We missed you at the croquet party.
对不起
Sorry.
希望这对你来说不会太尴尬
I- I hope this isn't too awkward for you.
不 不
No. No.
不 我一点都不尴尬
No, it's not awkward for me at all.
不 她需要个新保姆
No, um--she needed a new sitter
那时我上了大学 所以
when I went off to college anyway, so...
保重 好吗 很高兴见到你
You take care, okay? Nice to see you.
我要的是蚱蜢
I asked for a Grasshopper.
是吗
Did you?
对不起 坎德拉 这儿已经有主了
Oh, sorry, Kendra. It's taken.
这儿已经有主了 继续走
This one's taken. Keep moving.
我都不知道你有裙子
Oh, I didn't even know you owned a dress.
-有主了  -好了 雪莉
Taken. - All right, Shelly.
你需要冷静下来
You just need to calm down.
这是你第一次推销广告
This is your first advertising pitch
我只是想让它完美 对吧
and I just want it to be perfect, right?
是 它会的
Yeah, it will be.
你没看见我站在这里吗
Uh-uh. Can you not see I'm standing here?
罗杰
Roger.
艾琳 我喜欢这条裙子
Eileen, I love that dress.
嘿
♪ Hey ♪
天下精灵
♪ Three rings for the Elven kings ♪
铸三戒
♪ Underneath the sky ♪
地底矮人
♪ One for the Dark Lord ♪
得七戒
♪ On his dark throne ♪
一个错过的梦
♪ A missed dream ♪
现在该停下了
♪ Gotta stop it now ♪
燃烧的欲望
♪ The burning desire, yeah ♪
这么多虾
Mm. So many shrimp.
哦 还有大的
Ooh, and the big ones, too.
你穿的是什么
What are you wearing?
什么 你说的是 穿适合场合的衣服
What? You said "Dress for the occasion."
你看起来像是饥渴的有钱人
This looks like the "Rich and Horny" wardrobe.
那是因为这就是
That's because it is.
听着 要么是这个 要么是 维多利亚的泼妇
Look, it was either this or "Victorian Vixens."
请原谅我妹妹的不礼貌
Please excuse my sister's lack of manners.
我觉得你们看起来挺不错 我是雪莉
I think you look just fine. I'm Shelly.
嗨 雪莉 雪莉
Hi. Shelly. Shelly.
-雪莉  -姐姐还是妹妹
Shelly. - Older or younger?
某人的教养很好啊
Someone's been brought up right.
我得说 这地方
- Well-- - So, I gotta say, this place
并没有我想象的那么好
is not as nice as I thought it would be.
-这些树篱需要修剪  -那是因为现在是六月
The hedges need pruning. - Oh, that's 'cause it's June
鹪鹩还在那里筑巢
and the wrens are still nesting in them.
鹪鹩是一种棕色小鸟
我的庄园也有同样的问题
I have the same problem at my chateau.
-好  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
我们开始表演吧
Let's get this show on the road.
太好了 我在这里占了一桌
Oh, good, I have a table saved all right over here--
哦 库珀夫妇
Oh, the Coopers.
嘿 戴安
Hey, Dianne.
-干杯  -噢
all: L'Chaim. - Oh.
让我把你介绍给罗斯先生吧
Let's introduce you to Mr. Ross, okay?
谁在乎母马的屁股 它们是兔子
Who gives a mare's behind? They're bunnies.
那我们该怎么做 在人身上做试验吗
What are we supposed to do, test on humans?
说得好 罗斯先生
A good point as always, Mr. Ross.
这些激进分子精神错乱了
They're unhinged, these activists.
下一步是什么 禁止使用滴滴涕吗
What's next, a ban on DDT?
滴滴涕是一种有机氯类杀虫剂
先生们
Gentlemen.
我看到你为今晚化了妆
I see you put your face on for the evening.
哦 我只是画了一点眼线 仅此而已
Oh, I just wore a little eyeliner, that's all.
这位一定是大名鼎鼎的雷内蒂先生
This must be the famous Mr. Renetti.
是 你的俱乐部可真漂亮 先生
It is. You have a beautiful club here, sir.
树篱挺有意思
Lovely hedges.
是啊 它们每年这个时候都有点不守规矩
Yeah, well, they're a bit unruly this time of year.
女士们非常支持
The ladies are quite up in arms
-保护鹪鹩  -噢 她们啊
about protecting the wrens. - Oh, those ladies.
她们现在对每件事都有自己的看法
They have opinions about everything these days.
-是的  -她们让我的生意
- We do. - They've made my business
变得很有挑战性
quite...challenging.
-哦 我想是的  -我们觉得我们能帮到你
- Oh, I bet. - We feel we can help you.
你似乎已经解决了 是吧
You seem to have figured it out, hm?
过去五年增长了60%
60% growth in the last five years,
400万册
4 million circulation.
你做足了功课啊 先生
You've done your homework, sir.
是的
Yeah, he has.
这就是为什么我们相信《风骚女子》真的能帮到你
So that is why we believe that "Minx" can really
因为它是一个平台
help you because it is a platform--
好 好了 闲聊聊够了
Okay. Okay. Enough of the chit-chat.
但也许我们应该直接谈正事
But maybe we should get down to brass tacks.
好的 我很乐意
Yes, I would love that.
-我也是这样想的  -雷内蒂先生
My thoughts exactly. - Mr. Renetti,
我们到客厅去吧
let's adjourn to the lounge.
我希望你喜欢高斯巴雪茄
I hope you're a Cohiba man.
如果你有的话 我会抽的
If you got'em, I'll smoke 'em.
那么 待会儿见
I'll see you later, then.
我是说 婴儿油是很好的基础油
I mean, baby oil works great as, like, a base,
但如果你想要正宗的棕色 你必须
but if you wanna be really brown, you have to
要加起酥油 然后喷帕姆
add Crisco and then spray yourself with Pam.
亲爱的 我就是这么烤火腿的
Honey, that's how I roast a ham.
我还以为你是葡萄牙人
And here I thought you were Portuguese.
不不不 我是白人
No, no, no. I'm white as heck.
她白得像个幽灵
She's like a ghost really.
知道吗 斑比太有才了
You know what, Bambi is so talented.
她能用牙齿开啤酒瓶
She can open beer bottles with her teeth.
用一根痰把纸巾沾起来
Pick up tissues with ropes of spit.
-对  -哇撒
- Yup. - Wow.
-就这样  -都是和嘴有关系的吗
- There it is. - Are they all mouth related?
我两岁的时候舌头被断过
Well, my tongue was clipped when I was two.
-好的  -我会很多派对技巧
- Okay. - I have a lot of party tricks
但没什么实际技能
but not a lot of actual skills.
和你妹妹一起工作真是太棒了
And working with your sister is so amazing.
她在乎的事情太多了
I mean, she cares about so many things.
-是的  -我想有所作为
- Yeah. - I wanna make a difference.
你会有的
You'll figure it out.
埃莉诺·罗斯福一开始也是个甜心
Eleanor Roosevelt started out as arm candy too.
敬埃莉诺
To Eleanor!
是的
Yes!
天啊 你们的生活看起来真有趣
Oh, my God. Your lives seem so fun.
我的嘴只会大喊大叫
All I do with my mouth is yell.
你有兴趣在黄昏时游泳吗
Can I interest you in a twilight swim?
我没带泳装来
Uh, I didn't bring my suit.
不需要那玩意儿
You don't need one.
哦 你在开玩笑吧
Oh, you're kidding.
-真的吗  -真的
Really? - Yeah.
我得佩服你 你的钩下得真好
I gotta hand it to you, you set a nice hook.
对我来说 收轴相当容易
It was a pretty easy reel-in for me.
我是说 显然我不是钓鱼爱好者
I mean, obviously I'm no angling enthusiast,
但我想我可以从语境中理解这句话的意思
but I think I can get what that means from context.
他想要一些高档的护肤品线
He wants the inside cover for some fancy skin line
然后是半页的那个 我不知道
and then a few half-pages for, I don't know,
什么眼部凝胶 但是他同意了
some eye-related goo. But he's in.
看起来凯迪拉克和鱼子酱起作用了
It looks like Cadillacs and caviar are in play.
再见了 双头屌
Au revoir, le double dong.
天呐
Oh, my God.
还有一件事
One other thing is, uh,
罗斯先生想和斑比共度一夜
Mr. Ross wants me to toss in a night with Bambi.
你不是在暗示
Uh, you're not suggesting--
是 为了达成交易
I am. In order to close the deal,
他想和斑比去他的
he wants a night with Bambi at his--
我猜你可以把它叫做他在鸦林镇的 操宅
I guess you could call it his "fuck pad" at the Ravenswood.
但我会听你的
But I will defer to you.
我会让你决定接不接受这些条件
I'll let you decide if those terms are acceptable.
哈哈 真好笑
Ha ha, very funny.
这是他的地址和
This is his address and the code
后门密码
to get in the back entrance.
你可以自己试试
You could try it yourself,
准备好面对一个
just be prepared for a handsy old man
硬都只能硬一半的下流老头吧
who probably only gets semi-hard.
抱歉 孩子 但这张卡片代表了这些人的真实自我
I'm sorry, kid, but this card is who these people really are.
这不是音乐
This isn't music.
不 《伟大的美国歌曲集》
No, "The Great American Songbook,"
那才是音乐
now, that is music.
不 诗歌
No, poetry.
无论白天黑夜 你都是唯一
♪ Night and day, you are the one ♪
只有你在月光下
♪ Only you beneath the moon ♪
在阳光下
♪ And under the sun ♪
希望我没有打扰到你
Hope I'm not interrupting.
科尔·波特才是被你打扰的人
Cole Porter is who you're interrupting.
我听说我们要做生意了
I hear we're going to be in business.
你没听错 小姐
You heard right, young lady.
你的搭档 雷内蒂先生 很有头脑
Your partner, Mr. Renetti, got a good head on his shoulders.
所以我们应该用这个地址来签你的合同吗
So is this the address we should use for your contract?
我这辈子 你都是这个俱乐部的老大
All my life, you've lorded over this club.
我不得不听你们的祝酒词
And I have had to listen to your toasts and your agendas
你们的议程 你们关于
and your archaic rules about dressing modestly
穿着举止得体的陈旧规则
and acting with decorum.
我不知道你在暗示什么
I don't know what you're insinuating,
但很明显 你误解了现在的情况
but clearly, you have misread the situation.
所以你不是一个卑鄙的厌女者
Oh, so you're not a vile misogynist
为了做交易让人把一个人
who makes a deal to have a human being
送到他的床上吗
delivered to his bed?
没事的 各位
It's all right, everyone.
只是普里格小姐一时糊涂
It's just Miss Prigger in one of her tizzies.
嗯嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
那是罗斯先生在我12岁的时候
And that was just Mr. Ross' hand on my ass
用手摸我屁股 我那时刚刚赢得了青少年网球锦标赛
when I was 12 years old and won the Juniors Tennis Tournament.
你想知道我为什么再也不上球场了吗
You wanna know why I'm never on the courts anymore?
因为那次抓屁股让我不愿再打网球了
It's because that ass grab made me quit.
你们都不打算说点什么吗
Oh, none of you are gonna say anything?
你真丢人
You are an embarrassment.
幸好你父亲没能活着看到这一天
It's a good thing your father didn't live to see this day.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
你没事了
You're fine.
天啊 我想这么做很多年了
God, I've wanted to do that for years.
我甚至不知道可以同时折断三根肋骨
I didn't even know you could break three ribs at once.
道格告诉我他说了什么
Doug told me what he said,
所以我给了它一点额外的魅力
so I gave it a little extra oomph.
-新天赋啊  -噢
- So a new talent. - Ooh.
天呐 普里格
Jesus, Prigger.
谁能想到你还会出拳揍人
Who knew you could throw a punch?
我再也不能回这个地方了
I can never come back to this place.
我觉得我没意见
And I think I'm fine with that.
嘿 乔伊斯 当我
Hey, Joyce, when I, uh--
当我遇到那个人 意识到他可能真的会在
when I met that man and realized that he might actually
我们的杂志上做广告的时候 我不想骗你 孩子
advertise in our magazine, I'm not gonna lie to you, kid,
我
I got--
我真的很兴奋
I got really excited.
嗯
Yeah.
我是说 你不会以为我想
I mean, what, you don't think I want to, uh,
就是 和真正有钱的人
I don't know, be in business with people
做生意吧
who've got real money?
用别人的钱在棕榈酒吧勾搭
Chum it up at The Palm on somebody else's dime?
是啊 但是
Yeah, that's not--
我们现在的情况不是这样
that's not where we are, though.
不 但我相信我们会的
No, but I believe we will be.
你和我按我们的方式合作
You and me together on our terms.
听起来不错
I like the sound of that.
好
Good.
因为我需要你帮我个忙
'Cause I need you to do something for me.
天呐
Oh, God.
质感和尺寸都很丰富
There's so many textures and sizes.
这个的脉络很逼真
Oh, this one has a very realistic vein.
我有个主意 《假阳具--
Oh, I got an idea. How about, "Dildos.
当其他所有的广告商都说不的时候》怎么样
When every other advertiser says no."
我能问个疯狂的问题吗
Can I ask a crazy question?
让女人了解性玩具真的有那么糟糕吗
Is it really so bad to let women know about sex toys?
哪个女人会想要性玩具
What woman wants a sex toy?
我不知道谁会用
I don't know anyone who uses them.
-你知道的  -噢 是吗
- Uh, yes you do. - Oh?
-噢  -只有这样我才能
Oh. - Yeah, it's the only way I
到终点 你懂我的意思吧
can, um...get to the end, per se.
和莱尼不行吗
So not with Lenny?
不 我是说 做爱的感觉很好
No, I mean, sex feels nice, but I just--
但我需要能让我大脑空白的东西
I need something to push me over the edge.
很长一段时间
For a long time, I thought there was
我都觉得是我自己有问题
something wrong with me.
如果我知道有这些 帮手
If I'd been aware of these, um...helpers,
就是我刚结婚的时候
you know, when I was first married,
这样我就不用哭
it might have saved me a lot of tears
也不用带着假发和眼镜害怕得去趟市中心了
and a scary trip downtown with a wig and glasses.
我不知道
I had no idea.
好吧 我们又不谈这种事
Yeah, well, we don't talk about this kind of stuff.
也许我们应该谈谈
Well, maybe we should.
嗯 好吧
Yeah. Okay.
你最喜欢用什么方式自慰
Uh, what's your favorite way to masturbate?
天啊 不
Oh, my God, no.
对不起 小姐
Excuse me, Miss.
我刚告诉你的是非常私人的事
I just told you some very personal things.
只有我的美发师才知道的事
Things only my hairdresser knows.
不
No.
反正 我也不 就是
I d--I don't do it, anyway, so--
不怎么做 所以 就是
Not really. So it's just, you know--
这让我觉得
It makes me feel, um...
这太蠢了
Ugh. It's dumb.
所以你唯一能得到快感的方式
So the only way you can get pleasure
就是和男人一起吗
is when you're with a man?
这可不太女权 小乔伊
That's not very feminist, Joycie.
格洛丽亚·斯泰纳姆会怎么说
I mean, what would Gloria Steinem say?
我希望如果我有幸见到格洛丽亚·斯泰纳姆
I hope if I ever meet Gloria Steinem,
我们可以不用讨论自慰
we are not talking about masturbating.
我非常希望你们会讨论自慰
And I very much hope that you are.
她可能也有一些小妙招呢
She probably has a few tricks up her sleeve,
你懂我的意思吧
you know?
好吧 回头见
All right, I'll see you later.
用这个 开4档 好吧
Use this one. Level 4. Okay?
我发现很难意识到
♪ I found it very hard to realize ♪
你
♪ That you ♪
从我眼中偷走了爱
♪ Stole the love inside from my eyes ♪
天呐 天呐
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
天惹
Holy moly!
因为你所做的一切
♪ With everything that you do ♪
对我来说 我本可以成为你的流浪狗
♪ To me, I coulda been a stray for you ♪
世界 小心点
她来了
你让我神魂颠倒
♪ You turn me upside down ♪
你待我如小丑
♪ You treated me like a clown ♪
我 我没有读懂剧本字里行间的暗示
♪ I, I didn't read the play between the lines ♪
我把你想的那部分表演出来了
♪ I acted out the part you had in mind ♪
为了我 我把你想要的角色演得很好
♪ For me, I play the part you want so very well ♪
因为我是唯一一个看不出来的人
♪ 'Cause I'm the only one I couldn't tell ♪
你最擅长的就是装装样子
♪ That playing off was what you do so well ♪
你 你收留了我 我却不知道
♪ You, you took me in, I didn't realize ♪
把我拉向你并不意外
♪ Pulling me to you is no surprise ♪
因为你告诉我的一切都是谎言
♪ 'Cause everything you told me was a lie ♪